remarkety.com 2013-12-25

# Privacy Policy

### Interamind Remarkety Privacy Policy

Interamind Ltd. (“Interamind” or “us”, “our”, “we”) provides Remarkety, an automatic customer retention service (the “Service”). Interamind respects your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how Interamind uses any data and information is provided to Interamind through the Service. Interamind will not make your information available to third parties without your consent, subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Terms capitalized but not defined herein shall have the meaning set forth in the Interamind Remarkety Terms of Service, a current copy of which is available at [Terms of Service](http://imservice.local/terms/terms_conditions.html).

 **Information We Collect**

Interamind will have access to Identifying Information of your Customers, such as their name, address, email and activity history (such as purchase history) of Customers. In addition, entities that register to use our Service will be required to provide us with certain Identifying Information. Interamind also collects any Identifying Information contained in any message that you may send to Interamind. “Identifying Information” means information that can be directly associated with a specific individual or entity such as but not limited to a name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or information about activities directly linked to an individual.

In addition, Interamind may gather information regarding the system and browsing activity of Merchants that access the Service, such as the operating system and browser of such users or how a user interacted with the Service.

 **How we Protect Information**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Identifying Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Identifying Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **How we Use Information**

Except as expressly set forth herein, we will not share Identifying Information with third parties without the express permission of the individual identified in such information. We may use Identifying Information internally – for example, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to make Interamind more useful, to customize Interamind and personalize its content.

In addition, by analyzing all information we receive, including all information concerning use of the Service and the browsing habits of end user of websites that incorporate the Service, we may compile anonymous statistical information (“Statistical Information”). Statistical Information helps understand trends and customer needs, and we may use it to provide recommendations and suggestions to Merchants. Statistical Information is anonymous and we will not link Statistical Information to any Identifying Information. We may share such Statistical Information with our partners, without restriction, on commercial terms that we can determine in our sole discretion.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to a visitor's browser. The browser provides this piece of text to the device of the originating visitor when this visitor returns. Interamind uses cookies to help personalize your Interamind experience. A “persistent” cookie may be used to help save your settings and customizations across site visits. Also, if you log in to Interamind, such a cookie will be used to recognize you as a valid user so you will not need to log in each time you use Interamind. Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but you can change this setting so your browser either refuses all cookies or informs you when a cookie is being sent. Also, you are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. Please note that some features of Interamind may not function properly when cookies are disabled or removed.

 **Third Parties**

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy only describes the policies of Interamind. Interamind does not control how entities using the Service may make use of your information, including any Identifying Information. Interamind shall have no responsibility or liability for the collection, use or storage of any data by any other entity, including without limitation any potential or actual employer making use of the Service. You should not provide any information to any entity unless you are comfortable with the privacy policies of such entity.

 **Other Uses or Transfer of Your Information**

We will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities, regulatory or government bodies, or court order requesting or directing us to disclose any information, including any names and IP addresses of Merchants or any Identifying Information of Customers. We may use subcontractors that are located in countries other than your own, and send them information we receive. For example, we may send your information to any countries outside the United States or the European Economic Area. All our subcontractors will be subject to non-disclosure and non-use obligations. Nevertheless, some countries may have levels of protection of personal and other information which are not as high as in your country of residence or business. We may transfer our databases containing your Identifying Information if we sell our business or part of it. 

 **Changes**

Interamind may update this Privacy Policy from time to time - we encourage you to review it periodically.

 **Comments and Questions**

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at: [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3Evar%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy70656%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy70656%20=%20addy70656%20+%20'remarkety'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy70656%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy70656\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3Edocument.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3Edocument.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%3C/script%3E.)[info@remarkety.com](mailto:info@remarkety.com).

 _Last updated: January 2013_
